

 \searrow

eduardocsilva2000@gmail.com

+351 910597715

9

Porto, Portugal

eduardocsilva.github.io

in

linkedin.com/in/eduardo-csilva

github.com/eduardocsilva

SOFT SKILLS

Communication

Leadership

Teamwork

Flexibility

Proactivity

Independence

Problem Solving

LANGUAGES

Portuguese

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

English

Full Professional Proficiency

INTERESTS

Programming

Technology

Artificial Intelligence

Web Development

Reading

Music

Sports

Eduardo Silva

Informatics Engineering Student

An independent and self-motivated student pursuing a Bachelor's Degree in Informatics Engineering at Instituto Superior de Engenharia do Porto (current average grade: 17,8 / 20), with a strong background in Software Engineering and Web Development, as well as Data Structures and Algorithms. Strong team spirit and creativity due to the 9 years as a federated football player and 4 years of experience as a musician.

EDUCATION

Bachelor's Degree in Informatics Engineering Instituto Superior de Engenharia do Porto

09/2018 - Present

Current Average Grade: 17,8 / 20

- Software and Application Engineering
 - ng Systems Arquitecture and Administration
- Advanced Algorithms and Data Structures
- Linear Algebra and Computational Mathematics

Sciences and Technologies - High School

Escola Secundária de Valongo

09/2015 - 07/2018

Final Average Grade: 19/20

WORK EXPERIENCE

Member of Informatics Department

Núcleo de Estudantes de Informática - ISEP

03/2021 - Present Porto

Drum Teacher Academia Dó Ré Mi

09/2019 - Present Valongo, Porto

PROJECTS

Laboratory and Project 5 - Public Transport Planning and Management App (09/2020 - 01/2021) Technologies Used: Node.js, React/Redux, C#, .NET Core, SQL Server, MongoDB, UML, etc. (Grade: 19 / 20)

Laboratory and Project 4 - Factory Floor Management Application (03/2020 - 07/2020) Technologies Used: Java, C, JSON, XML, XSD, XSL, H2 SQL, UML (Grade: 19/20)

Laboratory and Project 3 - Ride-Sharing Management Application (09/2019 - 01/2020)

Technologies Used: Java, JPA, Oracle SOL, UML (Grade: 19/20)

Laboratory and Project 2 - Domestic Services Management Application (03/2019 - 07/2019)
Technologies Used: Java, JavaFX, UML (Grade: 17 / 20)

Laboratory and Project 1 - Social Network Analysis Application (09/2018 - 01/2019) Technologies Used: Java (Grade: 16 / 20)

CERTIFICATES

Machine Learning - Stanford University (Coursera) (08/2020 - 11/2020)

Introduction to Machine Learning (Supervised and Unsupervised Learning), Data Mining and Statistical Pattern Recognition

HARD SKILLS

Languages: Python, HTML, CSS, JavaScript/TypeScript, Java, C#, C, C++, Prolog

Frameworks & Libraries: Scikit-Learn, Tensorflow, FastAPI, Express.js, .NET Core, React, Redux

Databases: MongoDB, MySQL, MariaDB, SQL Server, Oracle SQL, H2

Testing: Unit, Integration, Smoke, API, End 2 End

OTHER SKILLS

Musician (10/2017 - Present)

Guitarist for 3 years, Ballroom Dancer for 2 years and Drummer for 1.5 years

Federated Football Player (08/2008 - 08/2017)

Goalkeeper for the clubs União Desportiva Valonguense (2008-2014) and União Desportiva Sousense (2014-2017)